Let's move onto the organic search channel.
我们转到免费搜索渠道
This is the traffic coming to your site by
这是你的网站因用户点击
clicking on a link in search engine results pages.
搜索引擎结果页面中的链接而获得的流量
An organic link not a page ad,
它们来自免费链接 而不是页面广告
because of Google's dominance in the search space.
由于 Google 在搜索领域中占有主导地位
Most of the traffic comes from the Google search engine,
所以大多数流量是来自 Google 搜索引擎
but other search engines are also included here.
但这份报告中也包含其他搜索引擎贡献的流量
For instance Yahoo, Bing, et cetera.
例如 Yahoo、Bing 等
Here we are back in the channel's report.
我们现在回到“渠道”报告
When looking into the organic search channel,
点击“免费搜索”渠道链接
we can find the report on the main keywords that users are searching
我们可以找到用户搜索时使用的主要关键字的报告
for that ultimately let them to click on a link to the store.
他们就是通过点击这些关键字返回的搜索结果链接来到了我们的商店
Note that a main keyword line says not provided.
请注意 这一行主要关键字显示为“未提供”
When users search using the Google search engine,
当用户使用 Google 搜索引擎发起搜索时
Google will protect users' privacy when they're logged in to other Google services.
如果他们已登录其他 Google 服务 例如 Google 邮件或 Chrome
Like for instance Google mail or chrome.
那么 Google 将会保护用户隐私
For a logged in user,
对于这些登录用户
Google does not pass information about a keyword to users
Google 不会将他们搜索的关键字信息
who are searching for unto the Google Analytics report.
传入 Google Analytics 报告中
So we are a bit in the dark about the keywords
所以我们无从知道具体是什么关键字
that lead to clicks on organic search results.
带来了这些免费搜索结果点击流量
Unfortunately, the majority of users are logged in.
不幸的是 大多数用户都登录了其他 Google 服务
The key words that are reported from not logged in users or from other search engines,
但通过未登录用户以及其他搜索引擎收集到的这些关键字
still reveal some interesting information.
仍然能够给我们提供一些有趣的信息
In this case, it looks like the keywords are all pretty generic.
在这个示例中 这些关键字似乎都非常宽泛
That's quite surprising.
我对这个结果感到很意外
I would have expected to see more product related terms
我本来以为会看到更具体的产品名称
like Google t-shirt for instance or Google mugs.
例如 Google T 恤或者 Google 水杯
Something may be going on,
搜索结果页面上可能出现某些
on the search results pages that makes people not click.
导致用户不去点击免费链接的内容
Let's try and take a look ourselves.
我们来看一下
This is the search engine results page for a search for Google T-shirt.
这是搜索“Google T 恤”关键字返回的搜索引擎结果页面
There are many links here to
页面中包含许多指向
the Google merchandise store so it looks like that is not an issue.
Google Merchandise Store 的链接 看上去这个没有问题
However there are also many image rich placements here.
然而这里还有许多丰富图片广告版位
The top ones are sponsored ads and these images
顶部这几个都是赞助广告
may distract users from clicking on the organic links.
它们会转移用户的吸引力 导致他们不去点击免费链接
If I were managing the Google all my merchandise store,
如果我负责管理 Google Merchandise Store
I would evaluate whether I should buy this keyword and
那我可能会考虑是否购买这个关键字
try to get my own sponsored ads to appear here as well,
并尝试在这里投放我自己的赞助广告
since this search engine results page is pretty competitive.
因为这个搜索引擎结果页面非常有竞争力
It is worth digging into the acquisition channels one by one this way.
我们有必要通过这种方式逐一分析每个用户获取渠道
Even when your user base is growing,
即便你的用户群在不断壮大
understanding the acquisition channels a bit better
通过深入了解用户获取渠道
can reveal interesting opportunities for further growth.
你也可能找到进一步壮大用户群的机会
Since we're talking about search,
由于我们是在讨论搜索
let's take a look at a paid search traffic next.
接下来让我们看一看付费搜索流量